1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), "Iphone 11")
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
45. custom.ProductHelper.addAnyAvailableProduct()
49. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
57. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
61. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
65. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
69. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)